Văn Đức Thanh

Frontend Developer



OBJECTIVE

I'm Văn Đức Thanh, working as a Web Developer. I have 4 years of experience in JavaScript, jQuery, React Js, Redux. I'm looking software companies where dynamic working environment to collaborate and contribute, where I can improve my communication, and technical skills to grow in a long-term career

EDUCATION

HCM City University of Technology

08/2012 - 01/2017

Major: Computer Science

GPA: 7.1

WORK EXPERIENCE

Metanet Asia

4/2020 - Present

Pyco Group

2/2019 - 3/2020

Sutrix Solution

1/2018 - 11/2018

Solazu

1/2017 - 11/2017

Engineer Software

- React Js
- Redux
- HTML, Sass
- Bootstrap
- Ant Design

Front-end Developer

- React Js
- Redux
- jQuery

Front-end Developer

- React Js
- HTML, CSS
- jQuery

Front-end Developer

- jQuery
- Bootstrap
- HTML, CSS

PROJECTS

TCM

4/2020 - 12/2020

Test case management

Task

- Enhance existing features
- Implement new features for web front end using React Js, React
- Implement component unit-testing
- Using Ant Design

Tech

- React Js
- Redux
- Ant Design
- Styled-component
- Unit test, Jest, Enzyme, React Testing Library

Movie

5/2019 - 11/2019

Movie

Task

- Implement new features
- Enhance existing features

Tech

- JavaScript
- React Js, Redux

Hotel Rating

6/2018 - 11/2018

Hotel Rating

Task

- User Sign up, Login Authentication
- Upload file
- Create CRUD API for new features, functionality
- Validation Form

Tech

- Node
- MongoDB
- React

Education •

5/2018 - 7/2018

Education

Task

- CRUD Rest API using Node Js, Express
- Follow improvement suggestions from technical lead based on code review
- Implement feature based on PSD and requirement

Tech

- React Js
- Node
- MongoBD

Abudhabi culture

1/2018 - 5/2018

Abudhabi's culture and history

Task

- Bring Photoshop / Sketch, assets exports, PSD to HTML
- Analyze requirements, implement features in the specification document

Tech

- Jade, Less
- Bootstrap
- jQuery
- Gulp

Travel

1/2017 - 5/2017

Travel

Task

- Landing Page
- Bring Photoshop / Sketch, assets exports, PSD to HTML

Tech

- jQuery
- Jade, Less
- Bootstrap

SKILLS

- JavaScript
- ReactJs
- Less, Sass
- HTML, Jade
- jQuery